Guide to the People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
- Pro-Animal Organizations, 31 linear feet
  - CA: Federation of Jain Associations (CA) (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - CA: Feminists for Animal Rights (CA) (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - CA: Ferrets Anonymous (CA) (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - CA: Free Willy Foundation (CA) (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - CA: Friends of the Sea Otter(CA) (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - CA: Friends of the Sea Lion (CA) (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - CA: Friends of the Wolf (CA) (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - CA: Fur-Bearer Defenders (CA) (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - CA: Good Shepherd Foundation, Inc. (CA) (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - CA: Gorilla Foundation (CA) (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - CA: Greyhound Friends for Life (CA) (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - CA: Greyhound Pets of America (CA) (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - CA: Greyhound Protection League (CA) (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - CA: Horse Power (CA) (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - CA: House Rabbit Society (CA)- 1 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - CA: House Rabbit Society (CA)- 2 of 2 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - CA: Humane Farming Association (CA)- 1 of 4 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - CA: Humane Farming Association (CA)- 2 of 4 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - CA: Humane Farming Association (CA)- 3 of 4 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - CA: Humane Farming Association (CA)- 4 of 4 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - CA: Hunt Sabateurs—USA (CA) (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - CA: In Defense of Animals (IDA) (CA)- 1 of 7 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - CA: In Defense of Animals (IDA) (CA)- 2 of 7 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - CA: In Defense of Animals (IDA) (CA)- 3 of 7 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - CA: In Defense of Animals (IDA) (CA)- 4 of 7 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - CA: In Defense of Animals (IDA) (CA)- 5 of 7 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - CA: In Defense of Animals (IDA) (CA)- 6 of 7 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - CA: In Defense of Animals (IDA) (CA)- 7 of 7 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - CA: International Dolphin Project (CA) (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - CA: International Wildlife Rehabilitation Council (CA) (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - CA: JIV DAYA (CA) (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - California Equine Council (CA) (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - California Horse Adoption and Protection Society (CHAPS) (CA) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - California Marine Mammal Center (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Against Farm Animal Abuse (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Against Leather and Fur (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Campaign for the Abolition of Angling (British; Pisces: Magazine of the Campaign for the Abolition of Angling, several issues from 1994 and earlier; also Hookup: Newsletter of the Council for the Prevention of Cruelty by Angling, 1981 and other issues.) (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Canada: Action Volunteers for Animals (Canada) (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Canada: Allies for Animal Rights (Canada) (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Canada: Anima (Canada) (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Canada: Animal Alliance of Canada (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Canada: Animal Defence League of Canada- 1 of 4 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Canada: Animal Defence League of Canada- 2 of 4 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Canada: Animal Defence League of Canada- 3 of 4 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Canada: Animal Defence League of Canada- 4 of 4 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Canada: Animal Liberation Collective (Canada) (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Canada: Animal Welfare Foundation of Canada (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Canada: Ark II (Canada) (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Canada: Association for Animal Rights (Canada) (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Canada: Association for the Protection of Animals (Canada) (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Canada: Association for the Protection of Fur Bearing Animals (Canada) (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Canada: Bear Watch (Canada) (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Canada: Beauty without Cruelty International (Canada) (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Canada: Canada Earthsave Society (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Canada: Canadian Farm Animal Care Trust (CANFACT) (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Canada: Canadian Federation of Humane Societies 1” (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Canada: Canadian Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Canada: Canadian Vegans for Animal Rights (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Canada: Canadians for Ethical Treatment of Animals 1” (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Canada: Citizens Organized for Animal Liberation (COAL) (Canada) (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Canada: Council for Laboratory Animals (Canada) (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Canada: Creatures Land, Air, Water Advocacy (CLAW) (Canada) (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Canada: Friends of the Dolphins, Inc. (Canada) (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Canada: Friends of the Wolf (Canada) (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Canada: Grizzly Project, The. (Canada) (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Canada: Hunt Enders, Inc. (Canada) (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Canada: Intensive Farming Review (BC, Canada) (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Canada: Kindness Club (Canada) (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Canada: Lifeforce (Canada) (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Canada: Mercy: Volunteers for Animals (Canada)- 1 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Canada: Mercy: Volunteers for Animals (Canada)- 2 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Canada: Miscellaneous/Canada (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Canada: Native/Animal Brotherhood (Canada) (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Canada: People Acting for Animal Liberation (PAAL) (Canada) (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Canada: Project Wolf (Canada) (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Canada: Sea Shepherd Society (Canada) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Canada: Students for Other Species (SOS) (Canada) (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Canada: The Animal Defence Anti-Vivisection (Canada) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Canada: World Society for the Protection of Animals (WSPA) (Canada) (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Canada: Zoocheck Canada (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Canadian, The, Wild Horse Sanctuary (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Candy Kitchen Rescue Ranch (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Captive Animals’ Protection Society (9 bound annual reports: 1988-89 - 1995-96. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Care for the Wild (UK) (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Cat Protection League (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Center for Applied Animal Behavior (CA) (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Center for Birds of Prey (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Center for Science in the Public Interest (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Center to Study Human-Animal Relationships and Environments (CENSHARE)(MI) (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Chesapeake Humane Society (VA) (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Chesapeake Wildlife sanctuary (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Chickens’ Lib (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Children for Wildlife (MT) (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Chile: Unión de Amigos de los Animales (Chile) (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - China: China Wildlife Conservation Association (China) (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - China: Miscellaneous/China (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Citizens United for Bears (MI) (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Clergy and Friends for Animals and Earth (NJ) (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Coalition Against the Horse Slaughter Trade (CA) (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Coalition to Abolish the Fur Trade (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Coalition to Abolish the Fur Trade (UK) (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Coalition to End Primate Experimentation (CA) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Coalition to Protect Animals in Entertainment (CA) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Colorado Horse Rescue (C) (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Committee for Dove Protection (CA) (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Committee for the Conservation and Care of Chimpanzees (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Committee to Ban Horse-Drawn Carriages (DC) (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Community Baboon Sanctuary (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Compassion in World Farming (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Concern for Helping Animals in Israel (Chai)-1 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Concern for Helping Animals in Israel (Chai)-2 of 2 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Congressional Friends of Animals (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Coördinating Animal Welfare (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Cornish Seal Sanctuary (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Cousteau, The, Society (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Crustacean Liberation Front (CA) (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Cuba: Cuban Association for the Protection of Animals (Cuba) (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Culture and Animals Foundation (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Curious Critters (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Cyprus: Cyprus Herpetological Society (Cyprus) (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Czechoslovakia: Hnutí za Osvobození Zvírat (Czech) (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Czechoslovakia: Miscellaneous/Czechoslovakia (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Czechoslovakia: Sloboda Zvierat (Czech) (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Dedicated and Everlasting Love to Animals (DELTA) (CA) (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Defenders of Wildlife (advocates against wolf hunting in Alaska, etc.) (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Denmark: Miscellansoue/Denmark, etc. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Dolphin Freedom foundation (FL) (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Dolphin Prouject (FL) (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Dolphins in the Wild (FL) (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Dolphins Plus (FL) (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Donkey Sanctuary (UK) (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Hadwen Trust for Humane Research (articles, misc. correspondence, etc. 1987-2001) (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Elephant Orphanage (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Elephant Sanctuary (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Elsa Wild Animal Appeal (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Entanglement Network (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Defense Fund (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Equine Trust Foundation (AZ) (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Equus Rescue and Sanctuary (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Evangelical Environmental Network (EEN) (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Exotic Cat Refuge and Wildlife Orphanage (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Exotic Feline Shelter (Michigan) (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Federación de Estidades Protectoras de Animales de Venezuela (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Ferret Unity and Reg. Org. (CO) List of all ferret breeders, clubs, etc. (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Ferrett Lovers Association (FL) (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Finland: Animalia (Finland) (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Finland: Koe-eläinten suojelu/pv (Finland) (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Finland: Our Common Environment (Finland) (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Finland: Vihreä Risti—Giröna Korset (Finland) (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Florida Panther Project (FL) (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Focus on Animals (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Fodents Alliance for Tolerance (CA) (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Foundation for Animal Protection (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Foundation on Economic Trends (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - France: Association Zoophile et Antivivisectionniste de la Jeunesse (France) (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - France: Federation de Liaisons Anti-Corrida (France) (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - France: Foundation Brigitte Bardot (France) (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - France: French Articles (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - France: Ligue Antivivisectionniste de France (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - France: Ligue Franccedil;aise Contre la Vivisection (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - France: Ligue Franccedil;aise des Droits de l’Animal (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - France: Ligue Internationale de la Protection du Cheval (France) (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - France: Miscellaneous (France)-1 of 2 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - France: Miscellaneous (France)-2 of 2 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - France: Oeuvre d’Assistance aux Bêtes d’Albattoirs (France) (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - France: Pro Anima (France) (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - France: Rassemblements des Opposants à la Chasse (France) (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - France: Robin des Bois (France) (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - France: Société Nationale pour la Défense des Animaux (France) (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - France: Société pour les Droits des Animaux (France) (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - France: Société Protectrice des Animaux (France) (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Friends of Animals (Connecticut)-1 of 5 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Animals (Connecticut)-2 of 5 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Friends of Animals (Connecticut)-3 of 5 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Friends of Animals (Connecticut)-4 of 5 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Friends of Animals (Connecticut)-5 of 5 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Friends of Animals Sanctuary (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Friends of Beaversprite (New York)- 1 of 2 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Friends of Beaversprite (New York)- 2 of 2 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Friends of Whales (FL) (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Friends Vegetarian Society of North America (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Frisky’s Wildlife and Primate Sanctuary (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Fund for Animals—Articles (clippings, articles, much anti-hunting materials, award recipients)-1 of 3 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Fund for Animals—Articles (clippings, articles, much anti-hunting materials, award recipients)-2 of 3 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Fund for Animals—Articles (clippings, articles, much anti-hunting materials, award recipients)-3 of 3 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Fund for Animals—Literature (publications)-1 of 2 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Fund for Animals—Literature (publications)-2 of 2 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Fund for Animals—Miscellaneous (reports re: endangered species, legislation, news releases)-1 of 3 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Fund for Animals—Miscellaneous (reports re: endangered species, legislation, news releases)-2 of 3 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Fund for Animals—Miscellaneous (reports re: endangered species, legislation, news releases)-3 of 3 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Fund for Animals, Inc—Newsletters (NY)-1 of 2 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Fund for Animals, Inc—Newsletters (NY)-2 of 2 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Fundación Amigos del Parque Zoologico las Delicias de Maracay (Zoo Amigos) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Fur Farm Animal Welfare Coalition (MI) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Gentle World, Inc. (FL) (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - George Washington University Ethics and Animal Society (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Germany 2" (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Germany: Bundesverein der Tierbefreier (Germany) (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Germany: Miscellaneous—German Groups (Box 43.1, Folder 1)
  - Germany: Miscellaneous—German Groups (Box 43.1, Folder 2)
  - Germany: Miscellaneous—German Groups (Box 43.1, Folder 3)
  - Gibbon and Gallinaceous Bird Center (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Gibbon Rehabilitation Project (Thailand) (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Gorilla Haven (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Gorilla Protection Project Sanctuary (Congo) (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Great Bear Foundation (MT) (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Greece: Friends of the Greek Bear (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Greece: Greek Animal Rescue (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Greece: Hellenic Animal Welfare Society (Greece) (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Greece: Miscellaneous /Greece (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - GreenPeace (DC) (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Greenpeace—Action Alert (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Greenpeace—Appeals (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Greenpeace—Articles (considerable number of clippings)-1 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Greenpeace—Articles (considerable number of clippings)-2 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Greenpeace—Fact Sheets (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Grenada: Grenada Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Granada) (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Greyhound Friends, Inc. (MA)-1 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Greyhound Friends, Inc. (MA)-2 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Greyhound Network News (AZ) (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Greyhound Protection League (MA) (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Greyhound Rescue Association (MA) (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Greyhounds as Pets (CO) (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Harbingers of a New Age (MT)-1 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Harbingers of a New Age (MT)-2 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Health Care Consumers Network (HCCN) (DC) (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Hidden Harbor Environmental Center (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Highveld Horse Farm (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Hog Haven (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Home for Unwanted and Abandoned Guinea Pigs (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Home for Unwanted and Abandoned Guinea Pigs, The (GA) (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Horse Haven (British Columbia) (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Horse Protection Association of Florida, The (FL) (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Horse Protection League (CO) (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Horse Rescue Sanctuary (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Howl Wildlife Clinic (Washington) (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Humane Organization for Retired Standardbreds (H. O. R. S. E.) (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Humane Organization Representing Suffering Equines (HORSE) (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Humane Society of the U.S.-Animal Activists Alerts (DC)- (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Humane Society of the United States—Articles (DC)-1 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Humane Society of the United States—Articles (DC)-2 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Humane Society of the United States—Miscellaneous (DC)-1 of 4 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Humane Society of the United States—Miscellaneous (DC)-2 of 4 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Humane Society of the United States—Miscellaneous (DC)-3 of 4 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Humane Society of the United States—Miscellaneous (DC)-4 of 4 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Humane Society of the United States—Regional Reports (DC) (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Hungary: Ahimsza Magyar Vegetársaság (Hungary) (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Hungary: Animal Caritas (Hungary) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Hungary: Miscellaneous (Hungary) (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Hungary: Ö-KOALA-P Foundation (Hungary) (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Hydes Institute of Range and American Mustang (South Dakota) (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Idaho: Grey Wolf Committee (Idaho) (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - IL: Chicago Herpetological Society (IL) (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - IL: Food Animal Concern Trust (FACT) (IL)-1 of 3 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - IL: Food Animal Concern Trust (FACT) (IL)-2 of 3 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - IL: Food Animal Concern Trust (FACT) (IL)-3 of 3 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - IL: Greater Chicago Ferret Association (IL) (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - IL: Greyhound Racers Recycled (IL) (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - IL: International Wildlife Coalition (IL) (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Illinois Hooved Animal Humane Society (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - India: All India Animal Welfare Association (AIAWA) (India) (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - India: Animal Conservation for Life (India) (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - India: Animal Lovers Club (India) (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - India: Animal Welfare Board of India (India) (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - India: Blue Cross of India (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - India: Kindness to Animals and Respect for Environment (India) (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - India: Meatless Day, The (India) (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - India: Miscellaneous/India-1 of 2 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - India: Miscellaneous/India-2 of 2 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - India: Sanjay Gandhi Animal Care Center (India) (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - India: Vegetarian Society of Delhi (India) (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Indiana Hooved Animal Humane Society (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Interfaith Council for the Protection of Animals and Nature (MI) (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - International Black Rhino Foundation (Texas) (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - International Center for Gibbon Studies (California) (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare (IFAW) (MA)-1 of 5 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare (IFAW) (MA)-2 of 5 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare (IFAW) (MA)-3 of 5 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare (IFAW) (MA)-4 of 5 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - International Fund for Animal Welfare (IFAW) (MA)-5 of 5 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - International Network for Religion and Animals (DC) (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Irwin Animal Rescue Center (South Africa) (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Israel: Animal Liberation Israel (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Israel: Anonymous Educational and Environmental Awareness Center (Israel) (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Israel: Committee for the Convention for the Protection of Animals (Israel) (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Israel: Hebrew Articles (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Israel: Israel Association Against Painful Experiments on Animals (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Israel: Israel Society for the Abolition of Vivisection (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Israel: Miscellaneous/Israel (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Israel: Nature Protection Society (Israel) (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Italy: Animal Amnesty (Italy) (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Italy: Comitato Europeo per la Protezione degli Animali da Pelliccia (Italy) (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Italy: Lega Anti-Vivisezione (L. A. V.) (Italy)-1 of 5 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Italy: Lega Anti-Vivisezione (L. A. V.) (Italy)-2 of 5 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Italy: Lega Anti-Vivisezione (L. A. V.) (Italy)-3 of 5 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Italy: Lega Anti-Vivisezione (L. A. V.) (Italy)-4 of 5 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Italy: Lega Anti-Vivisezione (L. A. V.) (Italy)-5 of 5 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Italy: Miscellaneous (Italy)-1 of 4 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Italy: Miscellaneous (Italy)-2 of 4 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Italy: Miscellaneous (Italy)-3 of 4 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Italy: Miscellaneous (Italy)-4 of 4 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Italy: Unione Animalista (Italy) (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Italy: Unione Antivivisezionista Italiana (Italy) (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Jane Goodall Institute for Wildlife Research, Education and Conservation (AZ) (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Japan Animal Welfare Society (Japan) (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Japan Anti-Vivisection Association-1 of 3 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Japan Anti-Vivisection Association-2 of 3 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Japan Anti-Vivisection Association-3 of 3 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Japan Bird Society (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Japan: Animal and Bird Protection Section (Japan) (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Japan: Animal Refuge Kansai (ARK) (Japan) 2” (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Japan: Earth Green Federation (Japan) (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Japan: Friends of the Earth (Japan) (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Japan: Miscellaneous (Japan)-1 of 3 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Japan: Miscellaneous (Japan)-2 of 3 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Japan: Miscellaneous (Japan)-3 of 3 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Japan: Save the Animals (Japan) (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Japanese Articles (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Japanese Society of Alternatives to Animal Experiments (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Jews for Animal Rights (MA) (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Jolene’s Horse Rescue (CA) (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Keepers of the Wild (Las Vegas) (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Kennedy Institute for Ethics (DC) (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Kenya: Environmental Liaison Centre International (Kenya) (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Kenya: Miscellaneous (Kenya) - Missing Folder (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Kids for Konservation (GA) (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Kids for Animal Rights and the Environment (KARE) (GA) (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Kind (Kids in Nature’s Defense) (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Korea Animal Protection Society (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Korea Animal Rescue Association (KARA) (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - KS: American Society of Crows and Ravens (ASCAR) (KS) (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - KY: Greyhound Connection (KY) (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Last Chance for Animals (CA) - 1 of 3 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Last Chance for Animals (CA) - 2 of 3 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Last Chance for Animals (CA) - 3 of 3 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Last Post (Connecticut) (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Latham Foundation (CA) (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Lava Lakes Bird Sanctuary (California) (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Life for God’s Stray Animals, Inc. (GA)- 1 of 3 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Life for God’s Stray Animals, Inc. (GA) - 2 of 3 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Life for God’s Stray Animals, Inc. (GA) - 3 of 3 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Limbe Primate Sanctuary (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Living Free (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Lost Acres (Ohio) (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Lovers of Rodents International (LORI) (CO) (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Lynx (anti-fur trade) (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Magnificent Baboons (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Manatee Protection League (FL) (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Marine Mammal Commission (DC) (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Marine Mammal Fund (CA) (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Massachusetts Audubon Society (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Massachusetts Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (MSPCA) 1” (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Massachusetts SPCA (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - MaxFund (CO) (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - MD: Alley Animals (MD) (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - MD: Alley Cats Allies (MD) (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - MD: American Backyard Bird Society (MD) (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - MD: Audubon Naturalist Society (MD) (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - MD: Center for Environmental Education (MD) - empty file (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - MD: Days End Farm (MD) (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - MD: Dolphin Coalition (MD) (Box 52, Folder 8)